They stole his guitar.
the guy is a musician,
he came here,
he doesn't have a guitar,
so i have a surprise for him
and he doesn't know it.
How are you?
Oh,
did you sleep well there?
I saw you singing,
bro,
touching the parades
for us to be able to realize its potential,
but you are without
use this one.
so, oh,
it starts.
this is a gift
for you.
sometimes we look for opportunity,
confuse,
I think we're being opportunistic,
because you will speak,
man i can sing
and it's a scream more than look at me notice.
and when we resolve
is to be the box and make our own creative space,
people who like your talent,
who like your work will start following you,
will start to see you
do you have this willingness to do so?
Yes,
actually
I've thought about doing this several times and try to do
which I don't understand very well.
it's my job.
I can only guide you,
say by where
it's with you,
brother let's go there and think of a place.
now bro three
first seconds
you have to get the person's attention.